novaswimwear.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Nova Swimwear understands that privacy is important to you and wants your experience online to be as enjoyable and safe as possible. This policy describes how the company handles your personal information generally and when you use the Site. This privacy policy applies to the company handling of personal information generally and when you use this site. The company is bound by the National Privacy Principles as set out in the Australian Privacy Act (Cth) 1988 as amended and the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993.

What Personal Information is collected by the company?

Visitors to the web site provide various kinds of information in several different ways. Some visitors choose to submit personal information through subscription and entry forms, enquiry forms and requests for more information, either through e-mails, response devices or other methods. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information including but not limited to, details such as your name, e-mail address or information about what you like and do not like. When booking services on-line or paying for other services, we may request your credit card number to complete the transaction or your mailing address to ensure delivery. The company will not collect sensitive information about you such as details of your race, political beliefs, religion or health. However this may be required where we are providing you with specialised services.

As you browse Nova Swimwear website third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information so that we can better understand what you are interested in. Marketing agencies can use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. The techniques our partners employ  **do not  collect** personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

This information will be recorded by the company and updated when additional information is supplied or upon request from you. The contact details of the company are available when you obtain services from the Bamboo Restaurant. Use of Personal Information The company uses the personal information collected to provide you with our services and to assist in making your experience with the company a satisfying one. Information is also collected to establish and maintain proper business records. Your personal information may also be used by the company to notify you about new products, services or promotions in the tourism, hospitality or services industries from time to time. Will your information be given to anyone else? All personal information collected by the company is only made available to those authorised individuals who need to handle that information for the purposes outlined in this policy. In some circumstances, personal information may also be disclosed outside the company. For example, we may disclose personal information to third parties to whom the company contracts out specialised functions (such as mailing houses and printing companies). In such cases we will require an undertaking from such persons to comply with the National Privacy Principles and Information Privacy Principles and do not use the personal information for any purposes beyond the scope of our contract with them.

The company will also disclose personal information when required by law and may disclose it when reasonably necessary to assist an enforcement body or to lessen or prevent a threat to individual or public health or safety. Use of Cookies The companies web site application may use cookies exclusively for session management. These temporary cookies serve to identify the user during each individual visit to the site ("session"). This is a built-in feature of Active Server Pages (ASP) technology. These cookies are temporarily stored in the user's browser throughout the course of each individual session. No other use is or can be made of the information contained in these cookies, and there is no trace of individual sessions.

For more information please contact [support@novaswimwear.com](mailto:support@novaswimwear.com)
